Guide to the 125th Street Branch records, 1904-2000
The New York Public Library. New York Public Library Archives.
125th Street Branch records
1904-2000
MssArc RG8 5845
5845
New York Public Library. 125th Street Branch
The New York Public Library. New York Public Library Archives. Stephen A. Schwarzman Building Fifth Avenue at 42nd Street, New York, NY 10018-2788
.5 linear foot 2 boxes
The 125th Street Branch of The New York Public Library was opened in 1904. The library building was designed by the architectural firm of McKim, Mead & White and was constructed with funds provided by Andrew Carnegie. Reports, administrative files and registration books documenting operations of 125th Street Branch of The New York Public Library.
The 125th Street Branch of The New York Public Library was opened in 1904. The library building was designed by the architectural firm of McKim, Mead & White and was constructed with funds provided by Andrew Carnegie.
Reports, administrative files and registration books documenting operations of 125th Street Branch of The New York Public Library.
Transferred from 125th Street Branch Library.
Advance notice required.
Box 2 closed to research.
New York Public Library. 125th Street Branch; Branch libraries -- New York (State) -- New York; Libraries -- New York (State) -- New York; Public libraries -- New York (State) -- New York
- 125th Street Branch Records, 1904-2000; 896545
  - Annual Reports - Branch, 1980-1989; 896546 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annual Reports - Children's, 1967-1973; 896547 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual Reports - Young Adult, 1981-1982; 896548 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Brochure, 1975; 896549 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - News Clippings, v.d.; 896550 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Opening, 1904; 896551 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Program Flyers, 1967-1973; 896552 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
  - Promotional Card, 1912; 896553 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Reader's Notification Card, 1912; 896554 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Branch Libraries Council visit, 2000; 896555 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Adult Registration Book, 1911-1919; 896556; Closed to research (Box 2, Volume 1)
  - Children's Registration Book, 1911-1913; 896557; Closed to research (Box 2, Volume 2)
  - Children's Circulation Statistics, 1906-1917; 896558; Closed to research (Box 2, Volume 3)